Remember me
Find myself all alone
In darkness without you
Now I can't turn away
From what I must do
You know I'd give
my life for you
More than words can say
I've shown you how
to love someone
I know you'll find a way
Say goodbye
Close your eyes
Remember me
Walk away
The sun remains
Remember me
I'll live on somewhere
in your heart
You must believe
Remember me
No way I can change my mind
I don't have the answers
If you could see
through my eyes
You'd let go of your fears
And though I have
to leave you now
With the thought of each other
I miss your touch
You call my name
I am with you forever
Say goodbye
Close your eyes
Remember me
Walk away
The sun remains
Remember me
With the change
we can't explain
Remember me
I'll live on somewhere
in your heart
You must believe
Remember me
You know I'd give
my life for you
More than words can say
I showed you how
to love someone
I know you'll find a way
Say goodbye
Close your eyes
Remember me
Walk away
The sun remains
Remember me
Be there to watch over you
Feel I'm gone
My heart lives on
Remember me
Don't you think
of this as the end
I'll come into your dreams
Remember me
Close your eyes....
Say goodbye....
Remember me
Say you will
Close your eyes....
Remember me
Say you will
Say goodbye