How many roads must a man walk down
Before you call him a man?
How many seas must the white dove sail
Before she sleeps in the sand?
Yes, and how many times
must the cannon balls fly
Before they're forever banned?
The answer, my friend,
is blowing in the wind
The answer is blowing in the wind
Yes, and how many years
can a mountain exist
Before it is washed to the sea?
Yes, and how many years
can some people exist
Before they're allowed to be free?
Yes, and how many times
can a man turn his head
And pretend that he just doesn't see?
The answer, my friend,
is blowing in the wind
The answer is blowing in the wind
Yes, and how many times
must a man look up
Before he can see the sky?
Yes, and how many
ears must one man have
Before he can hear people cry?
Yes, and how many deaths
will it take 'til he knows
That too many people have died?
The answer, my friend,
is blowing in the wind
The answer is blowing in the wind