There's something
happening here
Uh what it is ain't exactly clear
There's a man with
a gun over there
Uh telling me I got to beware
I think it's time we stop,
children, what's that sound
Everybody look
what's going down
There's battle
lines being drawn
And nobody's right if
everybody's wrong
Young people speaking
their minds
Are getting so much
resistance from behind
It's time we stop,
hey, what's that sound
Everybody look
what's going down
What a field-day for the heat
A thousand people
in the street
Singing songs and
they're carrying signs
Mostly say, hooray for our side
It's time we stop,
hey, what's that sound
Everybody look
what's going down
Paranoia strikes deep
Into your life it will creep
It starts when
you're always afraid
Step out of line, the
man come and take you away
We better stop, hey,
what's that sound
Everybody look
what's going down
Stop, hey, what's that sound
Everybody look
what's going...
You better
Stop, now, what's that sound
Everybody look
what's going...
You better
Stop, children,
what's that sound
Everybody look
what's going down...