Ooga chaka, ooga ooga
I can't stop this feeling
Deep inside of me
Girl, you just don't realize
What you do to me
When you hold me
In your arms so tight
You let me know
Everything's all right
I'm
hooked on a feeling
I'm high on believing
That you're in love with me
Lips as sweet as candy
Its taste is on my mind
Girl, you got me thirsty
For another cup o' wine
Got a bug from you girl
But I don't need no cure
I'll just stay a victim
If I can for sure
All the good love
When we're all alone
Keep it up girl
Yeah, you turn me on
I'm
hooked on a feeling
I'm high on believing
That you're in love with me
All the good love
When we're all alone
Keep it up girl
Yeah, you turn me on
I'm
hooked on a feeling
I'm high on believing
That you're in love with me
I'm hooked on a feeling
And I'm high on believing
That you're in love with me
I said I'm hooked on a feeling
And I'm high on believing
That you're in love with me