Woo ooh ooh ho ooh ooh hoo...
Ah ah ah haa haaa...
Woo ooh ooh hoo
ooh ooh hoo ooh...
Ah haa...
In the middle of the night
I go walking in my sleep
From the mountains of faith
To the river so deep
I must be looking
for something
Something sacred I lost
But the river is wide
And it's too hard to cross
Even though I
know the river is wide
I walk down every evening
and stand on the shore
I try to cross to
the opposite side
So I can finally find
what I've been looking for
In the middle of the night
I go walking in my sleep
Through the valley of fear
To a river so deep
I've been searching
for something
Taken out of my soul
Something I'd never lose
Something somebody stole
I don't know why I
go walking at night
But now I'm tired and I
don't want to walk anymore
I hope it doesn't take
the rest of my life
Until I find what it is
I've been looking for
In the middle of the night
I go walking in my sleep
Through the jungle of doubt
To the river so deep
I know I'm searching
for something
Something so undefined
That it can only be seen
By the eyes of the blind
In the middle of the night
Wee eeh eeh eeh hee
eh eeh eeh hee hee
Ya tha woo ooh ooh ooh ooh
ooh eh eeh eeh eeh hee hee hoo
Oh wo ho ho ho...
I'm not sure about a
life after this
God knows I've never
been a spiritual man
Baptized by the fire,
I wade into the river
that is running through
the promised land
In the middle of the night
I go walking in my sleep
Though the desert of the truth
To the river so deep
We all end in the ocean
We all start in the streams
We're all carried along
By the river of dreams
In the middle of the night
Ah ha...
Woo ooh ahh ah ah ah ah ah ah
Oh wo oh ho ah yea...
Oh oh oh oh ha ho ho...
Na na na na
Ah yeah
Ah...
Eeeh eeh eeh hee...
Oh oh oh oh oh ho...
Gloria...
It's not Cherie...
Eeh eeh eeh eeh eeh
ah ha ah ah...
Ah ah ha ha ha...