Come
Come take
Come take my
Come take my jour
Come take my journey
In
Into
Into night
Come
Come be
Come be my
Come be my shad
Come be my shadow
Walk
Walk at
Walk at my
Walk at my side
And
And when
And when you
And when you see
All
All that
All that I
All that I have
All that I have seen
Can
Can you
Can you tell
Can you tell me
Love
Love from
Love from pride?
I
I have
I have been
I have been wait
I have been waiting
all
all this
all this time
for
for one
for one to
for one to wake
for one to wake me
one
one to
one to call
one to call mine
So
So when
So when you're
So when you're near
all
all that
all that you
all that you hold
all that you hold dear
do
do you
do you fear
do you fear what
do you fear what you
do you fear what you will
do you fear what you will find?
As
As the
As the dawn
Breaks
Breaks through
Breaks through the
Breaks through the night
I
I move
I move on
For
Forev
Forever
Forever long
Forever longing
Forever longing for
Forever longing for the
Forever longing for the home
I
I found
I found in
I found in your
I found in your eyes
I
I will
I will be
I will be lis
I will be listen
I will be listening
for
for the
for the drum
to
to call
to call me
to call me ov
to call me over
far
far a
far away
far away from
my
my ten
my tender
my tender youth
and
and the
and the ver
and the very
and the very truth
show
showing
showing me
showing me what
showing me what I've
showing me what I've be
showing me what I've become
As
As the
As the dawn
Breaks
Breaks through
Breaks through the
Breaks through the night
I
I move
I move on
For
Forev
Forever
Forever long
Forever longing
Forever longing for
Forever longing for the
Forever longing for the home
I
I found
I found in
I found in your
I found in your eyes
Your
Your voice
saw
saw me
saw me through
saw me through the
saw me through the night